For Tiffany's hair I had to pre-treat her hair for hair color and that's the case for any hair color in order to achieve the best results.
You want to use a deep clarifying shampoo and make sure it says clarifying shampoo.
That gets rid of any residue that might be in the hair.
Any styling products, any hairspray buildup and sometimes there's a conditioner buildup.
That will keep your hair from coloring properly if you do not use a clarifying shampoo to get rid of that.
Then the next process that I did was a deep conditioner, a protein anything any conditioner that says protein on it.
You want to use a protein based conditioner.
Which is a very thick conditioner that will help fill in any dry areas of her hair.
So her hair color processes properly.
So I've pre-treated her hair for hair color so we can get the best results from her highlights.
So she's not going to have extra light spots extra dark spots.
It's evened the porosity of her hair and will make her hair ready for hair color.
So Tiffany will have beautiful highlights when we're done.